在这篇文章中，我们将学习一个更正式的数学概念
In this reading, we'll study a more formal mathematical idea
类实现抽象数据的含义
of what it means for a class to implement an abstract data
使用抽象函数的概念输入
type using notions of abstraction functions
以及表示不变性。
and representation invariance.
这些数学概念非常突出
These mathematical notions are eminently
软件设计实用。
practical in software design.
抽象函数正在运行
The abstraction function is going
给我们一个清晰定义质量操作的方法
to give us a way to cleanly define the quality operation
以及抽象数据类型
and abstract data type, which we'll talk about in more
深入未来的课程。
depth in a future class.
表示不变量将
The representation invariant will
更容易捕获由损坏的数据引起的错误
make it easier to catch bugs caused by a corrupted data
结构。
structure.
好 啊。
OK.
我们开始吧。
Let's get started.